

<Developer/> + Designer

)		97	3.5	95	4	.6	7	3														in			N/	C	HI	11	51		IP	H	EF	RF	W	/0	J	CI	K
~	ı	HE	LL	0(<u>a</u>	CI	HF		٥V	VC	J	C	IK	.N	ΙE	T					(_)	CHRISWOJCIK.NET															
			-			-	-			-	-			-	-	-	-	-	 	-	-	-		 -	-		-	-	-	-	-			-	-	-	-		-
													_	_										 	_			_											

16 Arlington Place - Kearny. NJ 07032

PROFILE: Driven and inventive professional with a diverse technical skill set. Have demonstrated ability to multitask in a fast-paced workplace. Possess a broad range of professional experience gained from working in both the corporate environment and with small teams. Designer and developer with a passion for crafting websites rooted in web standards, best practices, validation, and performance.

EDUCATION

POSTGRADUATE CERTFICATE, WEB DEVELOPMENT

New York University, December 2012
Courses include Web Architecture & Infrastructure, HTML & CSS, Javascript, PHP with MySQL

BACHELOR OF ARTS. POLITICAL SCIENCE

Pennsylvania State University, August 2007

CORE SKILLS & TOOLS

HTML5 / CSS3	
Responsive Design + Media Queries	
Javascript + JQuery	
PHP + My SQL	
Photoshop + Illustrator	

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE WEB DESIGNER, APR. 2011 - PRESENT

- Designed and coded a website for an online gaming community in HTML/CSS and developed a custom MVC-style framework for the back end, providing the group with a stronger visual presence and improving content management
- Designed marketing materials for Crohn's and Colitis Foundation of America local fundraising event
- Redesigned the website of the Radio Repertory Company of America for use in a preposed rebranding initiative

CONSULTANT, FOREST LABORATORIES, DEC. 2009 - Aug. 2012

- Developed improved procedures for organizing and filing project documentation and contracts for offsite storage
- Utilizing MS Access, VBA, and SQL, designed and built custom forms and queries according to the department's needs, allowing them to locate records for timely future retrieval

CAMPAIGN STAFFER. JUNE 2008 - Nov. 2009

- Handled in-house design work and coordination for campaign literature and media projects: newspaper and online ad placement,
 website banners, flyers, election day literature, etc.
- Performed daily updates to voter information databases, merged data from multiple sources, and performed tracking and data
 analysis to allow the campaign to target future field work
- Created a custom data sheet to improve the campaign's tracking of election day numbers, allowing staff and candidates to view and analyze results